Seino! Rattle Channel GOGO!
Yes, that's why today
I tried many things with my naked eye!
Yay!
I'd like to do it!
Hi!
Okay, um, this...
So far? Yes, the three of us on this side of the room are able to live our daily lives with contacts, but it would be really
It's really hard! They can't see anything, and they look like this. So, the three of us have tried many things, but I am sure things will be strange.
So, I asked Momoka-san, who has good eyesight, to join us because I felt uneasy with just the three of us. I'm looking forward to working with you.
How about your eyes?
My eyes are good, but the left one is better. It's like 1.5.
I am a leveechi. If you can feel how bad my eyes are, please.
Okay, so, Momoka, you're concentrating. First of all, you know, the basics. Normal people, they say. I'd like to go on. First of all, let's start with...
To the left. Right. Right. Right. Right. Down. Oh! Huh?
Uh, diagonally down on the left. Oh! Oh, yeah! Diagonal!
Right. What? What? Correct. Wow!
Up. Amazing! Left. What's that? You can see it in 2.0. What? That's amazing! Here.
Oh. Opposite? Left. Right. Up.
What? Left... right... slanted... hmmm...
I'm a bit out of practice, aren't I?
I can see 2.0 in the tracing, and next time I'll choose Yuri, wow!
I love your face
I'll be there every day kicking mobile this
Right diagonal abling me
Oh, no, no, no!
Okay...
Okay, this one
Um...
On the left.
Down there.
And this...
Down.
Diagonally to the left.
Left.
I can't see anything.
Then it's about 0.3.
Right.
Left.
Uh-oh.
Oops.
Perfect.
Diagonally left.
Down.
Hatena?
Right-right.
What's this?
Left?
Yes, left.
I think we're in a little bit of trouble here.
I think we're in trouble over here.
Left one's in trouble.
It's hard to tell.
I really don't get it.
Are you serious?
I really don't know.
It's both eyes. It's this way.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I really can't tell.
Come on.
Come on, Minamina.
Steady your eyes, Minamina.
Come on!
Go!
Hey!
Left.
To the right.
You want to switch?
Yes, sir.
Wait a minute.
Both eyes out.
This one.
This way.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm?
See? There's two circles coming out of it.
No, I don't see any circles.
Wait, what do you see?
All I see is a color.
I can tell there's something there.
No, I know. I know.
You're not seeing anything.
Maybe it's the first time... you can't see the top.
No, I thought...
I don't know.
I thought you were there.
I can't see.
No, you can't.
Maybe if you stand up, you'll see.
You're right. You do have one eye.
I'd know if I could see if you stood up.
If you had both eyes, you'd still be able to see.
You wouldn't know.
This could be bad.
Wait a minute... I couldn't tell you.
Crystal, wait a minute.
Suddenly they're round.
Wait a minute.
Here we go.
To the left.
Here.
Wait a minute.
Right?
Come on.
On your left shoulder.
I'm scared. - Oh, no.
It's down there.
What's this?
Right.
Oh, wow.
This one.
I can't see it anymore.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
The black's gone, too.
Is that it?
Down.
Adjust the light.
Diagonally up on the right.
Here.
Yes?
Popular.
Then why?
Is it on the left?
Yes, sir.
Down.
Left.
It's not good.
It's bad, isn't it?
I haven't had one of these in ages.
And inside, all the way up... black circles. This is bad.
Okay, here's the subject of our message game.
I'll connect them. Wait a minute.
I'm going to stretch my arms out.
Can I stretch my arms out?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Okay, okay.
Oh, what?
Oh, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I don't know. I don't know.
I saw something.
That's pretty embarrassing.
Okay, kya-chan, it's okay.
Yes, Kya-chan.
Wait a minute.
Ha-ha-ha.
Okay.
It matches this one.
Wait a minute.
Does it really match?
It's a perfect match.
It definitely matches.
I see it.
I got it.
All right. All right.
Here we go.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Delicious.
It's good.
It's good?
What's this?
It's good.
Okay, you got it?
Okay. - Okay.
I think I'm making a mistake.
Here we go. Okay.
Chittery chittery.
Acorns.
Donguri.
It's so sticky!
What's so chittery about it?
You said it was chattering.
Did you see the D?
And I thought it was beautiful.
Oh, that's what you thought?
Yes, it does look a little bit like beauty.
From that angle, it's just a little ripped.
From this side, it looks...
It looks like it's there.
It's fun.
Here we go.
Oh, my God.
What?
Hawaii.
This trick?
Let's go.
I don't see anything about that, do you?
Hey, girl.
Hey, guys.
No, guys.
It doesn't say "everyone.
No, it doesn't?
What? What?
It doesn't feel right, does it? At the end.
It's too hard.
Read it.
I don't know.
It says "read".
What?
What kind?
What is it?
Ice cream? Ice cream?
Do you want to get some ice cream today?
I want some.
Yes!
I want some!
But... but... but...
It's about two lines, right?
What?
One line.
Oh, one line?
One line?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What?
I really can't see.
Can I come in a little closer?
I feel like ice cream!
Oh, my God!
Not a big one, though.
No?
I'm in the mood for some ice cream.
I feel like eating.
I thought it was a nest
And then...
Hmm?
I know it's big.
I know.
It's big, but I can't see it.
Fire?
It doesn't say fire.
Some kind of fire.
It's on fire.
Ha!
Earth fire.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Isn't that some kind of fire?
Hey, it's a fire of some kind.
It's a fire of some kind.
It's a blowtorch.
The giant sea bream...
Fire.
Some kind of smoke.
No?
Wait a minute.
It's called something.
Meat.
Silk?
Huh? Silk? Silk? Silk?
Which one?
Can I have another one?
Can I have one more?
Silk.
Clothes!
What do you think?
Yes!
At such a close range, you know.
Okay, you got it?
Yes!
You got it?
That's how you do it?
Yeah, I didn't notice.
That's really funny.
No, I want to show everyone Peach's point of view.
Sure.
This is the most Momo point of view.
It's like I'm seeing things for the first time.
I'm trying my best to do it this way.
Okay, now, on this white wall
I'm going to put this Toumai chibi rubber on this white wall.
I'd like the three of you to look for it.
Surreal.
Everyone will look for it.
Isn't it close? Gentlemen.
Oh, by all means, no.
Oh, that's enough.
Yo!
There we go.
What is that, dirt on the wall?
Can I touch it? Can I touch it?
Okay, okay.
There it is. There it is.
What's that? How many are you wearing?
This one.
I thought they were trash.
I got one of these.
Look!
There it is.
Oh, my God!
People are going crazy for this one.
Four chains of these.
Oh, my God.
They're looking hard for something they've never seen before.
Amazing.
Okay, thank you for watching today.
If you think your eyes are that bad, please give us a high rating, subscribe to our channel, and comment.
I can see everyone's face.
Yes, please watch.
I'm watching.
Bye bye.
This time, I'm wearing Bigo's outfit.